bollykings.com 2012-06-21

# Privacy Policy

### Your privacy is critically important to us. At Bollykings.com we have a few fundamental principles:

 **Information we collect from our users**

This site does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals, for instance, when subscribing to our Newsletter. In particular, when purchasing a subscription, you must provide [contact](http://www.bollykings.com/contact/ "contact") information (such as name and e-mail address).

We do collect anonymous, aggregated data and provide it to our advertisers and other companies that we do business with for market research and statistical purposes. Bollykings.com may use such information to help determine ways to improve our site.

We do not provide, sell or lease personally identifiable information to any third parties. As an exception, to protect site visitors and the general welfare, the site will release personal information when necessary in order to comply with the law or regulatory authorities. If you have any questions or concerns regarding what is done with your information on any part of Bollykings.com, or would like such information deleted from our records, please e-mail us at admin [at] bollykings[dot]com

 **What are cookies? How do you use them?**

“Cookies” are text files that are used to collect information about visits that helps us create an overall profile of how visitors use our site, and how often they come. Cookies cannot be used to collect data from any user’s computer – cookies can only be used in conjunction with the site being visited.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some portions of Bollykings.com will not function properly if you do so.

For further information on cookies and their use, see the help instructions delivered with your browser or contact the browser’s manufacturer.

You also may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. Bollykings.com does not control those cookies and those cookies are not subject to this policy. Please note that the use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is common in the Internet industry.

 **Is the information you collect about me secure?**

We take every precaution to protect users’ information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, and unlawful destruction or accidental loss.

 **What about children using your site – is their privacy protected?**

Yes.  In accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), Bollykings.com does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent. If it is learned that such information has been collected without parental consent, that information will be deleted from the site’s database as quickly as practical or the child’s parent(s) will be contacted to obtain consent for the collection of the information.

And we encourage parents to get involved with their children’s online usage and to be aware of activities in which they are participating.

Finally, parents should be aware that if a child voluntarily discloses his or her name, e-mail address, etc. on various forums, or chat areas, such disclosure may result in unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should discourage your child from doing so.

 **What about my privacy on linked sites?**

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Bollykings.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website.

 **Online behavioral advertising (.OBA.) and/or multi-site advertising is occurring**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

By using this website, you consent to the collection of information as described in this policy.

 **Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Bollykings.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Bollykings.com’s sole discretion. Bollykings.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.
